http://hostedfx.com/pages/privacy_policy

HomeClient areaSitemapOur BlogContact us
live chat software
sales toll free 9am - 6pm est
(800) 657-8042
Cloud hostingCloud Hosting OverviewCloud Hosting PlansOS ListResell Our ServicesDedicated ServerDedicated Server PlansResell Our ServicesWeb HostingWeb Hosting PlansWeb Design & Software ToolsReseller HostingReseller Hosting PlansWeb Design & Software ToolsReseller Account ManagementMore ProductsOverviewColocation HostingCustom InfrastructureDomainsManaged ServicesMerchant Account ServicesSSL CertificatesResell Our ServicesAbout Hosted FXAbout UsAffiliate ProgramOur InfrastructureTestimonialsWhy UsResell Our ServicesSupport
1
Welcome to Hosted FX
9 Years Experience in Enterprise Cluster HostingWorld Class Data HostingNo Setup Fees, No Hidden Charges24/7/365 Technical Support Guarantee
tier 4 datacenter 6 carriersredundant 10G Internet100% uptime, guaranteed
4
Want to Make Money as Affiliate?
click here
Want to White-Label Resell Our Service?
Information:
This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect
from you, what we do with the information, and our
information security practices. If you have any questions
about our Privacy Policy, please contact us.
We may ask you to complete user surveys, and to provide
certain demographic information, such as age, gender,
special interests, etc. You do not have to provide this
type of information to use our service if you do not want to.
If you contact us for customer support, we may also ask you
for information about your operating system, software and
other technical matters.
When you visit our Web site we will capture your IP Address,
time of and duration of visit, and time and duration of the
pages on our Web site that you view. We may tie this
information to the personally identifiable information we
have about you.
We will also place a cookie that will identify you to us as
a repeat visitor or a customer when you visit our Web site.
See "What is a Cookie" below. We may tie this cookie to the
personally identifiable information we have about you.
[If we send you an e-mail, we may include a marker that will
allow to identify e-mail that is opened and viewed.]
Use of Personally Identifiable Information
We will use your personally identifiable information only as
follows:
For payment purposes and to provide customer support;
To announce special offers or provide other information
from time to time via e-mail. We may also send e-mail
announcing special offers by our third parties, but we
will not provide the third parties with your e-mail
address or other personally identifiable information.
If you do not wish to receive these e-mails, you may opt
out of future e-mails at any time by following the
instructions included in the e-mail.
To improve our service and the marketing of our service.
For example, we may use the information we gather from
user surveys, demographic data, and web site visits to
help us improve or target our Web site and customize
your visit.
We will not provide any personally identifiable information
about you to any other person other than:
a law enforcement or regulatory agency at their request;
a person or company who acquires our business;
third parties who perform services on our behalf (such
as payment processing), subject to the third party
agreeing with us that it will keep your personally
identifiable information confidential;
As otherwise needed to protect or enforce or rights or
the rights of others.
Use of Non-Personally Identifiable Information
We may share aggregate statistical data about our customers
with third parties, such as advertisers or suppliers. This
aggregate statistical data will not identify you personally.
What is a Cookie?
A "cookie" is an alphanumeric identifier that is unique to
your browser. The cookie will identify your browser to us
when you visit our web site so that we may customize your
visit.
Security of Your Information
We store your personally identifiable information and payment
information inside an encrytped database to ensure maximum
protection for you
Children's Privacy
Our service is not available to children under the age of 13,
and we will not intentionally maintain information about
anyone under the age of 13.
Our BlogTerms of ServicePrivacyClient areaContact us
Copyright © 2005 - 2020 HostedFx.com.
All Rights Reserved
